Yes! Are you kidding me? The left? Are you insane?
Police officers!
Look, okay, look at LA right here. You think those stand-down, uh, those stand-down...
You think the LAPD are a bunch of liberal Marxists?
No, but I think they listen to liberal Marxists who tell them what to do.
I think they listen to who signs their paychecks at the end of the day who are liberal Marxists.
Can I just check, because you're doing lots of little diversions.
We both agree Donald Trump's pro-crime, you're just fine with it.
Is that the position? That's what you've said so far for about five minutes.
I don't agree with your definition of crime.
What's your definition of crime?
Stomping on a police officer's head is not a crime.
That's your definition of crime, as the Native American.
I am Native American.
If you say so.
So, going back to the topic at hand, we have different definitions of crime because you're
talking about...
That's convenient.
There's a criminal code in this country.
It's not about what's convenient.
It's called the U.S. Criminal Code.
You know what, let's focus on what we agree on.
That's what everyone focuses on.
I'm sure you and I actually agree on a lot more than you are.
Do we agree that people shouldn't stomp on police officers' heads? Can we agree on that?
I'm not...
If you don't agree on that, then I really think this conversation is kind of pointless.
No, because first of all, you're saying what? That the police have the authority, that they're
given the authority.
I don't accept the authority that's been given by liberal...
It's a very conservative position.
I think...
I call the conservative a pro-police.
Then you don't know what a real...
But we redefine crime.
Hey, listen, you're in a room with juggernauts right now, okay?
We redefine crime.
We redefine conservatives.
I'm telling you right now, you are going to be blown open if you think that my position
is wrong, right?
Yeah, if we're going to struggle with the English language for the next couple of hours,
then yeah, we struggle.
What you're up against right now, okay?
A hundred percent.
Yeah.
Newsflash, the conservatives are liberal to me, okay?
The Republicans, the Libertarians, all those mainstream people, there might as well be
leftists to me, okay?
That's how far to the right I am.
Do you understand my position?
I kind of guessed it when you sat down.
So when you say about obeying police, why would I give the authority to police?
Do you know here, do you know you're in America?
Do you think Donald Trump should be pardoning nine members of Congress who committed financial
crimes?
Are you pro-financial crime?
All right, pause.
Pause.
I think the people who clapped you have voted you out.
All right.
Head back to your seat.
You've been voted out by the majority.
Nice to meet you.